{
    "subject": "resource/Gauhati_University",
    "predicate": "property/motto",
    "object": "Vidyana Sadhayeta",
    "human_readable": "The motto of Gauhati University is Vidyana Sadhayeta.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8628360629081726,
            "question": "What is the motto of Gauhati University?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8450784683227539,
            "question": "Does Gauhati University have a motto?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7698453068733215,
            "question": "Is the motto of Gauhati University unique?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7268692255020142,
            "question": "How is the motto of Gauhati University displayed?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7045581340789795,
            "question": "In what language is the motto of Gauhati University written?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6565030217170715,
            "question": "What does 'Vidyana Sadhayeta' mean?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6468839645385742,
            "question": "What value does the motto of Gauhati University emphasize?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.3055787682533264,
            "question": "What role does the motto play in the university's identity?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.08135498315095901,
            "question": "Can you give examples of other universities with mottos?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.07617318630218506,
            "question": "Why do universities often have mottos?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The motto of Gauhati University is Vidyana Sadhayeta.",
            "html": "dbpedia_2424_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you give examples of other universities with mottos?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2424_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What role does the motto play in the university's identity?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2424_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What value does the motto of Gauhati University emphasize?",
            "html": "dbpedia_2424_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2424_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2424_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2424_28.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2424_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2424_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2424_51.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2424_6.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2424_74.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2424_75.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_2424_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here's the structured JSON response:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. The documents mention that the motto of Gauhati University is indeed \"Vidyana Sadhayeta\", and also provide further context and explanations for this motto, such as its meaning and significance."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\nThe documents provide multiple references confirming that the motto of Gauhati University is indeed \"Vidyana Sadhayeta,\" which translates to \"Achievement through Learning\" or \"Knowledge.\""
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "The Least Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}